[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 64, "question": "What is it about the particular chemistry of you five now you think that's been so you successful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "RB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 65, "answer": "You said it, when you said the C word.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Is actually likely that this is going to happen now from all that you see?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "And I really would like to change the word fear and just replace with it a healthy concern.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What do you think about the possibility of a direct hit on Haiti or even just very extensive rain damage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I think there's a lot of rain.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Haiti"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Are we going to see issues like abortion come into the fore or is it going to be swept away by the economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I mean, the economy is issue number one, two, three, four and five in this election, even though these other issues have come and been part of the dialogue every day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Do you think that's fair?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Well, and probably even more than that is that he's not look like us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "Or do you think it's an easy bit of rhetoric that actually what you're looking at is historical positions of the Republican Party that are just slowly going slightly out of fashion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I think that what's more important is that we bring the candidates on, we bring both parties on, and we let the audience make that decision for them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "What is your gut feeling about what real Americans care about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "JJ", "NNPS", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "I believe it's the economy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Tell me when you get, you know, a run of things like the convention now then the election, what do you think collectively you guys need to bring as a show to the American audience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "I think we have to be able to offer the widest range of story and sample that we can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2007"]}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 265, "question": "But are you scared in yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "After you've gone through breast cancer as I did in 2007, and unfortunately, this is because of some of the treatment, saved my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "And she's is a remarkable woman, isn't she, the way that she's been dealing with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Unbelievable.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "I mean, George, for you, guys, does it get better than that, the morning TV battle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "It was pretty amazing because -- like you said, it's something that hadn't happened in so many years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "What do you want to do with the show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I want to make it better.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Let me ask you, Lara, what do you feel collectively has made the difference here between you and \"The Today Show\" this year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I think it's what we touched on all show.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Lara"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Do you all hate each other behind closed doors?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I love that you picked on me for this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "So once you got a chance to sample it, how could you not choose that show?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "We don't take joy in what's happening in other places.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBG", ":", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", ":", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "When you made that speech, what was going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "It was great to be able to talk about him in so fitting -- in so fitting a way and before so many people that -- for whom he would be happy that I was in front of and for the reason I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "In bed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "In bed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "What do you read?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I'm reading the history of Islam.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Do you read \"In Style\" magazine in bed, George?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Of course I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "I can just pick up the ruins.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "RBS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What on Earth are you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "That might be the question that I've heard the most, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "Is the Rocket firing on all cylinders?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "The Rocket is almost firing on all cylinders.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "This is what the real game plan is, isn't it, Roger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Yes, everybody is saying that.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Roger"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120823pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "I want to come back out and show people what I'm still made of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Well, a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]